# ERICA CHAVEZ

818.310.4925 / erica.chavez25@gmail.com / ericachavez.me

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

LA based graphic designer with 4+ years of experience. Expert at developing innovative and fresh designs while staying true to the company's brand and identity. Team player who can work in a fast-paced, deadline driven environment. Winner of the 2016 American Graphic Design Award by Graphic design USA.

#### •

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### The City of Glendale

Graphic Designer / Feb. 2015 - Present / Glendale, CA

- Collaborate with different city departments to provide simple and attractive digital/print media.
- Establish the creative vision and presence for various city outreach campaigns.
- Leverage environmental and way-finding designs to connect people and businesses to the city.
- Convey complex data and statistics into compelling yet approachable infographics.
- Communicate directly with print shops for proofs and final products.

#### The Center for Visual Communication (VISCOM)

Graphic Designer & Project Manager / Feb. 2014 - Jan. 2015 / Northridge, CA

- Pitch detailed proposals, estimates, timelines, and presentations for clients and design team.
- Highlight solutions with clients throughout the design process to achieve satisfaction.
- Collaborate with a team of designers via drafts, critiques, and finalized artwork.
- Strategize and design in depth projects by performing audits and extensive research.
- Organize and package production work.

# **Twenthieth Century Fox**

Graphic Designer - Intern / Sep. 2014 - Dec. 2014 / Los Angeles, CA

- Deliver consistent and professional designs by intergrating into the company's culture and visual principles.
- Design and update social media content for the public.
- Create collateral event material through print and web.



#### **EDUCATION**

## **California State University Northridge**

Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Design Aug. 2010 - Dec. 2014



## SKILLS

Creative Thinking / Typography / Print / Digital
Adobe Illustrator / Photoshop / InDesign / After Effects / Microsoft Office
Bilingual in English / Spanish